

SHAGOTO BHAKAT

Frontend Web, UI/UX and Graphic Designer

About Me

I am Shagoto Bhakat. I am a Frontend Web Designer with an experience of 7 years. I design all kinds of Website and Software with Reactjs and Nextjs. I also design with Bootstrap, Material UI, Tailwindcss, Chakra-ui, Theme-ui, Ant design and various kinds of Animations. I am currently working as a Web & Graphic designer on an IT company.

- +8801741148841
- shagoto.bhakat@gmail.com
- Dhaka, Bangladesh
- <u>LinkedIn</u>

LANGUAGE

- Bangla
- English

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript
- React JS, Next JS, jQuery
- MySQL, Oracle, Firebase
- GitHub, Git
- Designing:

PSD to HTML

Bootstrap

Material UI

Tailwindcss

Ant Design

Adobe XD

Figma

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Indesign

Webflow and Canva

EXPERIENCE

Intern
Jamuna Bank limited
01/08/2018 - 30/11/2018

Designer
Creative IT Institute
01/01/2019 - 31/12/2019

Graphics and Web Designer PERFECT FOOTWEAR LTD.

01/09/2020 - Currently working

I have experience of working as a freelancer as well.

PORTFOLIO

As a web designer, I have designed few websites which are now on live. The websites are given below—

- PERFECT FOOTWEAR LTD.
- TASHDID Printing And Packaging
- **JUNAINA Shoe Trading**

Some other design which are designed by me

My Work

EDUCATION

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB)

B.Sc. Computer Science and Engineering (CSE)

2014-2018 CGPA: 3.23 out of 4.00

Rajshahi Model School & College Rajshahi

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

2013 Group : Science GPA: 4.80 out of 5.00

Rajshahi Model School & College Rajshahi

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

2011 Group : Science GPA: 4.88 out of 5.00

ACADEMIC PROJECTS

Restaurant Management System (Web Application)

Online Application for Billing, Food Storage, Book Table, Employee Management

Code Igniter, HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

Trello Management

Project Management Application
Visual Studio, C#, MySql.

Hospital Management System

Using the oracle database. This project use for hospital staff, DR & administrative panel

Database

Scenery of Bangladesh

Using open GL, create scenery of Bangladesh

Computer Graphics

THESIS

Framework to Deliver Documents in A Secured Way

Description: Comparing the existing algorithms for Unstructured Big Data to replace with the newer ones and proposing a new model that reduces overhead

Domain: Data Management Systems

INTERESTS

- Music and Singing
- Web
- Travelling
- Show Movie

PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name : Nimai Bhakat

Mother's Name: Roni Rani Bhakat

Date Of Birth: 10 November, 1996

Gender : Male

Marital Status: Married

Nationality : Bangladeshi

NID No : 912 824 9647

Religion : Hindu

➡ Blood Group : O-

Permanent Address: C/O-Holding No 09, Chindipur, Betiapara, Rajshahi, P.O.- G.P.O, P.S.- Rajpara, Dist.-Rajshahi

Present Address: 36, Pioneer Road, Segunbagicha, Dhaka-1000

REFERENCES

DR. Tabin Hasan

Professor of Science and Technology

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB)

MD. Ezazul Islam

Associate Professor of Science and Technology

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB)

DECLARATION

I am confident that I have the ability to work with proper responsibility on one's own imitative. I will try my best to perform my duties according to the desired satisfaction of the authority.

I am the undersigned, hereby declare that the above information is true and I will be responsible for any wrong information.

SHAGOTO BHAKAT

Date: